Picture Collection LSC.0099.a
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Cholmodeley, Mary, 1859-1925., 1 item (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Christrian, H.T., 1 item (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Christy, Howard Chandler, 1873-1925., 1 item (Folder 4)
- Chula Vista, Calif., 2 items (Folder 5)
- Churches., 25 items (Folder 6)
- Churchill, Sir Winston Leonard Spencer, 1874-1965., 2 items (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Churchill, Winston (by C. Beaton)., 1 item (Folder 6)
- Cilo, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Circus -- Views., 3 items (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Claremont College, Claremont, Calif. -- Views., 23 items (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Clark, Champ (James Beauchamp) 1850-1921., 6 items (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Clark, Precentacion Ballester De., 1 item (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Claxton, Kate., 1 item (Folder 13)
- Clemenceau, Georges Eugene Benjamin, 1841-1929, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 14)
- Clemens, Samual Langhorne, 1835-1910., 1 item (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Clemens, Samual Langhorne., 5 items (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Clemens, Samuel. (Folder 1)
- Cleveland, Stephen Grover, Pres. U.S., 1837-1908., 3 items (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Clothing and dress -- Views., 56 items (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Cloudcroft, N.M. -- Views., 39 items (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Clovis, N.M. -- Views., 31 items (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Coachella Valley, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Coachella, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 20)
- Coal Mines and Mining -- Views., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Coasts -- California., 13 items (Folder 23)
- Cobb, Irving Shrewsbury, 1876-1944., 1 item (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Cochran, Jacqueline -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Cody, Iron Eyes, 1904-1999, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Cohen, Alfred M., 1859-1949, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Cohn, J. B., 1 item (Folder 28)
- Coit, John Eliot, 1880-1976, -- Portrait., 2 item (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Colas -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Cole, Cornelius., 8 items (Folder 31)
- Coleman, Wanda (1946 - 2013)., 3 items (Folder 34)
- Collins, Mortimer, 1827-1876., 1 item (Folder 32)
- Collins, Wilkie., 2 items (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Colman, Ronald Charles, 1891-1958 -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Coloma, El Dorado Co., California, 4 items (Folder 36)
- Colorado -- Views., 45 items (Folder 3)
- Colorado Desert -- Views., 2 items (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Colorado River Aqueduct., 1 item (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Colorado River., 1 item (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Colorado Springs, Colo., 105 items (Folder 1)
- Colorado University., 21 items (Folder 2)
- Columbia River, 5 items (Folder 5)
- Columbia, California., 10 items (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Comfort, Will Levington, 1878-1932., 1 item (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Compton, Karl Taylor, 1887-1954., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Compton-Burnett, Ivy, 1892-1969. (Folder 2)
- Conant, James Bryant, 1893-1978, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Conejos, Colo., 4 items (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Conference Press -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Congress of Industrial Organizations. Political Action Committee, California -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Conkle, Earl Judson., 1 item (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Connally, Thomas Terry, 1877-1963., 1 item (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Contzen, Fritz., 1 item (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Cook, James, 1728-1779 -- Portrait., 11 items (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Coolidge, Calvin, pres. U.S., 1872-1933., 14 items (Folder 16)
- Coolidge, William Augustus Brevoort, 1850-1926., 1 item (Folder 17)
- Cooper, James Fenimore, 1789-1851 -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Cooper, John T., 1 item (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Cooper, Sarah Brown., 1 item (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Copper Mines and Mining -- Views., 21 items (Folder 21)
- Corbett, Jame J., 1866-1933 -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Corcoran, California., 8 items (Folder 23)
- Corelli, Marie, 1855-1924., 4 items (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Cork Industry -- Views., 7 items (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Cornell University -- Views., 2 items (Folder 26)
- Corning, Calif. -- Views., 12 items (Folder 27)
- Cornwell, Dean, 1892-1960, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 28)
- Coronado National Forest, Arizona -- Views., 4 items (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Coronado., 24 items (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Coronel Family., 7 items (Folder 31)
- Cortes, Hernando, 1485-1547, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 1)
- Cosmopolitan Productions Inc., 5 items (Folder 2)
- Costa, Sr Michael, 1810-1884, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Cota Family -- Portrait., 4 items (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Coulter, Frank -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 5)
- Coulterville, Calif., 2 items (Folder 6)
- Couts, Cave Johnson, 1856-1943., 4 items (Folder 7)
- Covarrubias, Jose Maria, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Cowan, Robert Ernest, 1862-1942., 5 items (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Cowboys, 3 items (Folder 10)
- Coy, Albert Wayne, 1903-1957., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Crackenthorpe, W., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Crater Lake National Park -- Views., 4 items (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Crater Lake National Park -- Views., 21 items (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Creede, Colo., 20 items (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Cremony, John C., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Cridland, E.L., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Croker, John Wilson, 1780-1857, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Crothers, Rachel, 1878-1958, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Crowley Lake., 3 items (Folder 20)
- Crowley, Aleister, 1875-1947, -- Photograph., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Crowninshield, Francis Welch, 1872-1942., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Cruikshank, George, 1792-1878, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Cuesta Pass, San Luis Obispo Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Cullom, Shelby Moore, 1829-1914, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Cummings, Calif. -- Views., 5 items (Folder 25)
- Curie, Mme. Marie (Sklodowska), 1867-1934., 2 items (Folder 26)
- Curran, Dennis., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Curtis, Cyrus Hermann Kotzschmar, 1850-1933., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Czechoslovakia -- Views., 3 items (Folder 29)
- Daggett, Calif. -- Views., 24 items (Folder 30)
- Daggett, John M. -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Dairy Plants -- Views., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Dakin, Susanna, (Bryant), 1905-1966., 4 items (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Dalton Family -- Portrait., 5 items (Folder 34)
- Daly, Carroll John, 1889-1958, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 35)
- Damrosch, Walter Johannes, 1826-1950, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 37)
- Dams -- Views. (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Dams -- Views., 60 items (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Dana Point, Calif., 7 items (Folder 38)
- Danby, Frank., 1 item (Folder 39)
- Dancers -- Views., 8 items (Folder 40)
- Darame -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Darfuille, Marie Julie., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Darwin, Charles Robert., 1 item (Folder 44)
- Davenport, L.N., 1 item (Folder 45)
- Davenport, Marcia (Gluck), 1903-1996., 1 item (Folder 46)
- Davies, Marion, 1897-1961., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Davis, James G., 1935-2000, -- Portrait., 8 items (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Davis, Jefferson C., 1828-1879, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 50)
- Davis, Jefferson, 1808-1889., 2 items (Folder 49)
- Davis, John William, 1873-1955., 1 item (Folder 51)
- Davis, William Heath., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Dawes, Charles Gate, 1865-1929., 3 items (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Dawson's Book Shop, booksellers, Los Angeles -- Views., 1 item (Folder 54)
- Daytona Beach, Florida -- Views., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 55)
- De la Ramee, Louise, 1839-1908, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Death Valley National Monument., 18 items (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Debs, Eugene Victor, 1855-1926., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Del Mar, Calif. -- Views., 40 items (Folder 5)
- Del Monet., 5 items (Folder 6)
- Del Monte Sporting Club of 1898 -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Dell, Floyd, 1887-1969, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Delta, Colo. -- Views, 25 items (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Dematteis Family -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Deming, N.M. -- Views., 36 items (Folder 11)
- Denmark -- Views., 2 items (Folder 9)
- Dentzel, Carl Schaefer., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Denver -- Views (University of Denver)., 11 items (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Denver, James William, 1817-1892, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Denver, Juvenile Court of City and County of Denver -- Views., 22 items (Folder 15)
- Denver., 61 items (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Denver. Colorado Woman's College -- Views., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Depew, Chauncey Mitchell, 1834-1928, -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 18)
- DePew, Elise (Hegeman) -1893., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Deschanel, Paul eugene Louis, pres. France, 1856-1922., 1 item (Folder 20)
- Deserts., 41 items (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Devils Tower National Monument, Wyoming -- Views., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Devore, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Devore, Sy, 1907-1966, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Devos, Julius Emil, 1848-1937., 1 item (Folder 25)
- Dewall, Wolf von, 1882- -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Dewey, George, 1837-1917., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 27)
- D'Garmo, H., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Dickens, Charles, 1812-1870, - Characters -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 30)
- Dickens, Charles, 1812-1870., 4 items (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Diday, Fran?ois, 1802-1877., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Dillion, Fannie C., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Dillion, Richard Hugh, 1924- -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Disney, Walt, 1901-1966, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Disneyland, Anaheim, Calif. -- Views., 14 items (Folder 4)
- Dix, John Adams, 1798-1879., 1 item (Folder 5)
- Dixon, Frederick., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Dixon, Maynard, 1875-1946, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Dixon, Willis Milnor, 1846-, 1 item (Folder 8)
- Dobie, James Frank, 1888-1964., 8 items (Folder 9)
- Dodge, Grenville Mellen, 1831-1916., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Dodge, John Mason, 1853-1951., 11 items (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Dodson, James Hillsay -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Doheny, Edward L., 1856-1935, -- Portrait., 5 items (Folder 13)
- Domesday Book., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Dominguez Family -- Portrait., 4 items (Folder 15)
- Donaldson, Will -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Donner Lake, Calif. -- Views., 5 items (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Donner Pass, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 18)
- Dore, Gustave., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Dorrington, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 20)
- Douglas, Donald Wills, 1892-1981, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Downey, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Downey, John Gately., 4 items (Folder 23)
- Dresden -- Views., 2 items (Folder 24)
- Dryden, William G., 2 items (Folder 25)
- Duarte, Calif., 11 items (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Duka Family Photographs., 12 items (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Dumas, Alexandre, 1803-1870., 2 items (Folder 28)
- Dumas, Alexandre, fils, 1824-1895, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 29)
- Dumke, Glenn S., 1917-1989., 1 item (Folder 30)
- Dunant, Jean Henry, 1828-1910, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Duncan, Isadora, 1878-1927, -- Portrait. (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Duncan, Isadora, 1878-1927., 2 items (Folder 32)
- Dunsmuir, Calif. -- Views., 8 items (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Dupre, Marcel, 1886-1971., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Durango, Colo. -- Views., 13 items (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Durfee, C.A. -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Durfee, Lydia, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 37)
- Durham, Philip, 1912-1977, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 38)
- Durrell, Lawrence, 1912-1990, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 39)
- Dutch Flat., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Duval, Robert Carson., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Eagle Rock, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 42)
- Earthquakes - California, Southern -- Views., 6 items (Folder 43)
- Eastman, George, 1854-1932, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 44)
- Eastman, Joseph Bartlett, 1882-1944., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Eaton, Fred., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Eaton, Helen., 1 item (Folder 2)
- Eaton, Nellie (Burdick)., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Eccles, Marriner Stoddard, 1890-1977., 1 item (Folder 4)
- Echo Canyon, Utah -- Views., 5 items (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Echo Rancho, Ontario, Calif., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Eclipses -- Views., 19 items (Folder 7)
- Edendale (Los Angeles, Calif.), 4 items (Folder 8)
- Edeson, Robert L., 1868-1931., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Edgeworth, Maria, 1767-1849, -- Portrait., 6 items (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Edinburgh., 6 items (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Edison, Thomas Alva, 1847-1931, - Laboratory -- Views., 6 items (Folder 12)
- Edison, Thomas Alva, 1847-1931., 1 item (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Edward VII, King of Great Britain, 1841-1910, -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Edward VIII, King of Great Britain, 1894-1972., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Edwards, Amelia Ann Blandford, 1831-1892., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Egypt -- Views., 56 items (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Einstein, Albert, 1879-1955., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Eisenhower, Dwight David, Pres. U.S., 1890-1969, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 18)
- El Cajon Valley, Calif., 4 items (Box 15, Folder 19)
- El Centro, Calif. -- Views., 86 items (Box 15, Folder 20)
- El Molino Viejo -- Views., 5 items (Box 48, Folder 8)
- El Monte, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 31)
- El Moro National Monument, N. Mex. -- Views., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 32)
- El Porvenir, N.M. -- Views., 3 items (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Eldora, Colo. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 21)
- Eldridge, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Electric Power Production -- Views., 16 items (Folder 23)
- Elephant Butte Dam, N.M. -- Views., 3 items (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Elevators -- Views., 22 items (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Elias, Jacob., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 1926- -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Elliott (William B.) cabin, Santa Rosa, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Elliott, Walter, 1842-1928., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Eloffe, madame., 21 items (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Elroy, James, 1948-, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Elsinore, Calif. -- Views., 36 items (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Ely, Nev. -- Views., 25 items (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Embudo, N.M. -- Views., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo, 1803-1882., 4 item (Folder 38)
- Emma, Consort of Kamehameha IV, King of the Hawaiian Islands, 1836-1885, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 40)
- English antiquities - forgeries -- Views., 7 items (Box 15, Folder 42)
- English, Thomas Dunn, 1819-1902., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Entertainers - United States -- Portraits., 9 items (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Entertainers, Afro-American -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 43)
- Escher Painting - German War Scenes. (Folder 2)
- Estes Park, Colo. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 1)
- Estudillo Family -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Eureka Springs, Ark. -- Views., 20 items (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Eureka, Calif. -- Views., 5 items (Folder 3)
- Eureka, Colo. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 4)
- Evans, Edmund, 1826-1905, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 6)
- Evergreen, Colo. -- Views., 1 item (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Ewell, Richard S., 2 items (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Ewing, Majl, 1903-1967, -- Portrait., 8 items (Folder 9)
- Expositions and Fairs -- Views., 4 items (Folder 10)
- Fadiman, Clifton, 1904-1999., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Fairbanks, Harold Wellman, 1860-1952, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Fallbrook, Calif. -- Views., 5 items (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Fallon, Nev. -- Views., 29 items (Folder 14)
- Faraday, Michael, 1791-1867., 1 item (Folder 15)
- Farjeon, Benjamin Leopold, 1833-1903., 1 item (Folder 16)
- Farley, James Aloysius, 1888-1976., 1 item (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Farragut, David Glasgow, 1801-1870, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Farwell, Arthur George, 1872-1952., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Faure, Gabriel Urbain, 1845-1924, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 20)
- Favary, Ethelbert -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 21)
- Feather River Inn, Blairsden, Calif. -- Views., 18 items (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Feliz Family -- Portrait., 4 items (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Fenn, George Manville, 1831-1909, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Fermin Huarte, F., 1 item (Folder 25)
- Ferrers, Marmion Edward, 1813-1884, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Festivals - California., 2 items (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Feuchtwanger, Marta Leoffler, 1891-1987, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Field, Eugene., 1 item (Folder 29)
- Field, Marshall, 1834-1906, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 30)
- Field, Rachel Lyman, 1894-1942, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 31)
- Figueroa Family -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Filmore, Millard, Pres. U.S., 1800-1874, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Fire engines -- Views., 5 items (Folder 34)
- Firola -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 35)
- Fischer, Emil -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 36)
- Fisher, George Park, 1827-1909, -- Portrait., 7 items (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Fitch, Henry Delano, 1799-1849, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Fitts, Buron Rogers, 1895-1973, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 39)
- FitzGerald, Edward, 1809-1883, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 40)
- Fitzgerald, Percy Hetherington, 1834-1925, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 41)
- Fitzsimmons, Cortland, 1893-1949., 4 items (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Flagstad, Kirsten, 1895-1962., 1 item (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Flagstaff, Ariz., 4 items (Folder 44)
- Flanagan, Edward Joseph, 1886-1948., 1 item (Folder 45)
- Flavin, Martin -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 46)
- Fleming, William Sherman, 1865-, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Flint, Benjamin., 1 item (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Flint, Thomas., 1 item (Folder 49)
- Flintridge Country Club., 1 item (Folder 50)
- Floods - Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Folder 51)
- Floriston, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Flowers., 24 items (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Flying Saucers -- Views., 1 item (Folder 54)
- Foch, Ferdinand, 1851-1929., 1 item (Folder 1)
- Foley, John Henry., 1 item (Folder 2)
- Folsom, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Forbes Family -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Ford Ord, Calif. -- Views., 45 items (Folder 18)
- Ford, Gerald R. -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 5)
- Forman, Henry James, 1879-1966., 11 items (Folder 6)
- Formes, Karl -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Forster, John, 1812-1876, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Forsyth, John, 1780-1841, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Fort Bayard, N.M. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 10)
- Fort Bidwell, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 11)
- Fort Bragg., 25 items (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Fort Collins, Colo. -- Views., 35 items (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Fort Defiance., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Fort Humboldt., 2 items (Folder 15)
- Fort Monroe, Va. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 16)
- Fort Morgan, Colo. -- Views., 38 items (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Fort Ross, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Fort Tejon, Kern Co., Calif., 2 items (Folder 20)
- Fort Yuma., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Fortas, Abe, 1910-1982., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Fortuna, Calif. -- Views., 5 items (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Foshay, James A., 4 items (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Foster, Stephen Clark, 1820-1898., 4 items (Folder 25)
- Fox, William, 1879-1952., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Foxen, William Domingo., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Fraenkel, Michael, 1896-1954, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 17, Folder 31)
- France -- Views. (folder 1 of 2), 123 items (Box 17, Folder 28)
- France -- Views. (folder 2 of 2), 98 items (Folder 29)
- France, Arm?e - Recruiting, enlistment, etc. - World War, 1914-1918, -- Views., 6 items (Folder 30)
- Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Frasher, Burton, 1888-1955., 32 items (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Freeman, Daniel, 1837-1918., 1 item (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Fremont Family -- Portrait., 18 items (Folder 4)
- French Research Foundation, Los Angeles -- Views., 19 items (Folder 5)
- Fresno, Calif. -- Views., 33 items (Folder 6)
- Friedrich Karl, prince of Prussia, 1828-1885., 1 item (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Frost Protection -- Views., 5 items (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Froude, James Anthony, 1818-1894., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Fultz, Francis Marion, 1857- -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 10)
- Gadski, Johanna, 1872-1932., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Gailland -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Gallup, N.M. -- Views., 29 items (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Galsworthy, John, 1867-1933., 1 items (Folder 14)
- Gand Canyon National Park -- Views. (folder 3 of 4), 38 items (Folder 1)
- Garcia Family -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 16)
- Garcia, Francisco., 1 item (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Garden of the Gods, Colo. -- Views., 47 items (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Gardens., 5 items (Folder 18)
- Garfias Family -- Portrait., 4 items (Folder 19)
- Garfield, James Abram, pres. U.S., 1831-1881., 3 items (Folder 20)
- Garibaldi, Giuseppe, 1807-1882, -- Portrait., 5 items (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Garvanza., 1 item (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Garvey, Marcus Mosiah, 1887-1940, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 23)
- Gauley Bridge, W. Va., 16 items (Folder 25)
- Gaulle, Charles de, 1890-1969, -- Portrait. (Folder 6)
- Gaviota Pass, Calif., 4 items (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Geddes, Norman Bel, 1893-1958, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Gelcich, Vincent, 1829?-1885., 2 items (Folder 27)
- General Motors Corporation., 47 items (Folder 28)
- George Pepperdine College, Los Angeles -- Views., 10 items (Folder 30)
- George VI, King of Great Britain, 1895-1952 - Coronation -- Views., 10 items (Box 93, Folder 8)
- George VI, King of Great Britian, 1895-1952, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 18, Folder 29)
- George, Walter Franklin, 1878-1957., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Georgetown, Colo., 1 item (Folder 32)
- Georgia -- Views., 3 items (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Gerhardt, Elena, 1883-1961, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Germans in the Philippines -- Portraits. (folder 1 of 2), 38 items (Folder 2)
- Germans in the Philippines -- Portraits. (folder 2 of 2), 28 items (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Germans in the Philippines., 95 items (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Germany. (folder 1 of 2), 236 items (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Germany. (folder 2 of 2) (Folder 5)
- Geyserville, Calif., 12 items (Folder 6)
- Giannini, Amadeo Peter, 1870-1949., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Gibson, John., 1 item (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Gilbert, Edward., 1 item (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Gilbert, Harlow, 1840?- -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Gilman Hot Springs, Calif., 8 items (Folder 12)
- Gilman, Daniel Coit., 4 items (Folder 11)
- Gilmoor, William, 1882-1938, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Gilroy Hot Springs, Calif., 3 items (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Gilroy, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 14)
- Giovanni, Nikki, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 16)
- Girardin, Delphine (Gay) De, "Mme Emile De Giraradin", 1804-1855., 1 item (Folder 17)
- Gish, Lillian, 1896-, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Gitchell, James A., 1 item (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Gladstone, William Ewart, 1809-1898 -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 20)
- Glamour photography., 4 items (Folder 21)
- Glass Manufacture -- Views., 52 items (Folder 1)
- Glassell, Andrew., 5 items (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Glen Ivy Hot Springs, Calif. -- Views., 10 items (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Glendale., 47 items (Folder 3)
- Glendora, Calif. -- Views., 22 items (Folder 5)
- Glenwood Springs, Colo. Views., 27 items (Folder 6)
- Godeffou -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Godowksy, Leopold., 3 items (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von, 1749-1832., 4 items (Folder 9)
- Gold Mines and Mining -- Views., 2 items (Folder 10)
- Gold Ray Dam, Ore. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Golden, Colo. -- Views., 43 items (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Goldmark, Rubin., 1 item (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Goldstone, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Folder 14)
- Gompers, Samual, 1850-1924., 1 item (Folder 15)
- Gonzales Family -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 16)
- Gonzales, Calif. -- Views., 4 items (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Goodman, John, III., 2 items (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Gordon, John Brown, 1832-1904, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Goudy, Frederick William, 1865-1947., 1 item (Folder 20)
- Gounod, Charles Fran?ois, 1818-1893, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 21)